Guide to the Eastmont Human Services Center records 1960-2003
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Correspondence
  - Region I Developmental Disabilities (DD) Division, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 25)
  - Dallas, Scott, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 26)
  - Srsen, Doug, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 27)
  - Selman, Cathy, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 28)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 29)
  - Surveys, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 30)
  - University of Montana, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 31)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 32)
  - Wurm, Jaci, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 33)
  - Auditor Information, 1985 (Box-folder 7 / 34)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1985 (Box-folder 7 / 35)
  - Board of Visitors, 1985 (Box-folder 7 / 36)
  - Boese, Gail M., 1985 (Box-folder 7 / 37)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1985 (Box-folder 7 / 38)
  - Central Office – Memos, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 1)
  - Department of Institutions, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 2)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 3)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 4)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 5)
  - Hoover, Jerry, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 6)
  - Rotering, Nick, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 7)
  - South, Carroll V., 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 8)
  - Developmental Staff, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 9)
  - Diede, Carole, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 10)
  - Disaster Drill, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 11)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 12)
  - Eastmont Echo, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 13)
  - Fire Drills, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 14)
  - Goodell, David, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 15)
  - Habilitation, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 16)
  - House Bill 909 Advisory Council, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 17)
  - Hammer – All Staff Memos, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 18)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 19)
  - Help Wanted, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 20)
  - Holm, Patricia, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 21)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 22)
  - Job Service, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 23)
  - Jones, Perry, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 24)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 25)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 26)
  - Lyon, Gary, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 27)
  - MPEA Status Change, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 28)
  - MPEA Union, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 29)
  - Medicaid, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 30)
  - Montana Veteran’s Home, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 31)
  - Seline, Gloria, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 32)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 33)
  - Recreation Memos, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 34)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 35)
  - Scott, Dallas, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 36)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 37)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 38)
  - Srsen, Doug, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 39)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1985 (Box-folder 8 / 40)
  - Board of Visitors, 1986 (Box-folder 8 / 41)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1986 (Box-folder 8 / 42)
  - Proposed Changes in Program, 1986 (Box-folder 8 / 43)
  - Certificates Received, 1986 (Box-folder 8 / 44)
  - Department of Institutions, 1986 (Box-folder 8 / 45)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 1)
  - Currie, Jim, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 2)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 3)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 4)
  - Hoover, Jerry, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 5)
  - South, Carroll V., 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 6)
  - Department of Public Health and Human Services (DPHHS), 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 7)
  - Developmental Staff, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 8)
  - Diede, Carole, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 9)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 10)
  - Eastmont Echo, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 11)
  - EPP Long Range Building Program, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 12)
  - Fire Drills, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 13)
  - Habilitation Staff, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 14)
  - Hammer – All Staff Memos, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 15)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 16)
  - Holm, Trish, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 17)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 18)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 19)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 20)
  - Lyon, Gary, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 21)
  - MPEA Union, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 22)
  - Medicaid, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 23)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 24)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 25)
  - Recreation, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 26)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 27)
  - Reorganization, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 28)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 29)
  - Rosin, Sherry, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 30)
  - Schedule, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 31)
  - Seline, Gloria, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 32)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 33)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 34)
  - Surveys, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 35)
  - Srsen, Doug, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 36)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 37)
  - Whitford, Beverly, 1986 (Box-folder 9 / 38)
  - Board of Visitors, 1987 (Box-folder 9 / 39)
  - Training – Helena Budget, 1987 (Box-folder 9 / 40)
  - Contracts and Information, 1987 (Box-folder 9 / 41)
  - Department of Institutions, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 1)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 2)
  - Currie, Jim, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 3)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 4)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 5)
  - Hoover, Jerry, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
  - South, Carroll V., 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
  - Diede, Carole, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 8)
  - Fire Drills, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 9)
  - Habilitation Staff, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 10)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 11)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 12)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 13)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 14)
  - Jessen – Staff Memos, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 15)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 16)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 17)
  - Lyon, Gary, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 18)
  - Medicaid, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 19)
  - MPEA Union, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 20)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 21)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 22)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 23)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 24)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 25)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 26)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 27)
  - Shanley, Cynthia, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 28)
  - S.I.C. Notebook Pages, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 29)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 30)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 31)
  - Sveen/Frenzel/Rosin, 1987 (Box-folder 10 / 32)
  - Veterans/Handicap Preference Information, 1987 (Box-folder 11 / 1)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1987 (Box-folder 11 / 2)
  - Whitford, Beverly, 1987 (Box-folder 11 / 3)
  - Berry, John, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
  - Board of Visitors, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
  - Chapter 1, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
  - Contracted Services, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
  - Laundry, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
  - Department of Institutions, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 9)
  - Anderson, Bob, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 10)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 11)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 12)
  - Redfield, Rusty, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 13)
  - South, Carroll V., 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 14)
  - Dattilo, John (Dr.) – Penn State Workshop Information, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 15)
  - Degel, Peter J. (Dr.), 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 16)
  - Developmental Disability (DD), 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 17)
  - Donation Sheets Received, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 18)
  - Family Services, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 19)
  - Fire Drills, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 20)
  - Green Thumb Program, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 21)
  - Habilitation, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 22)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 23)
  - Hammer – Miscellaneous Incoming, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 24)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 25)
  - In-Service Training, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 26)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 27)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 28)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 29)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 30)
  - Medicaid, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 31)
  - Mental Health Information, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 32)
  - Montana Developmental Center, 1988 (Box-folder 11 / 33)
  - MPEA Union, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 1)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 2)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual Updates, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 3)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 4)
  - Pulse, Tunk, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 5)
  - Eastmont Proposed Changes, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 6)
  - Eastmont Proposal for Non-Americans(?), 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 7)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 8)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 9)
  - Recreation Schedules (Weekends), 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 10)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 11)
  - Schleien, Stuart J., 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 12)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 13)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 14)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 15)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 16)
  - Sveen, Ann, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 17)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 18)
  - Whitford, Beverly, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 19)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 20)
  - Berry, John, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 21)
  - Board of Visitors, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 22)
  - Certificates Received, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 23)
  - Chapter 1, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 24)
  - Contracted Services, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 25)
  - Degel, Pete, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 26)
  - Department of Institutions, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 27)
  - Anderson, Bob, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 28)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 29)
  - Currie, Jim, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 30)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 31)
  - Personnel, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 32)
  - Redfield, Rusty, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 33)
  - South, Carroll V., 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 34)
  - Donation Sheets Received, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 35)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) Council, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 36)
  - Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council (DDPAC), 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 37)
  - Family Services, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 38)
  - Fire Drills, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 39)
  - Habilitation, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 40)
  - Hammer – Miscellaneous Incoming, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 41)
  - Hammer – Staff Memos, 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 42)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 1)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 2)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 3)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 4)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 5)
  - Mast, Jane, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 6)
  - Michelson, Keith, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 7)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 8)
  - MPEA Union, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 9)
  - Old Mom Policies, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 10)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 11)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 12)
  - Porter, Charles, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 13)
  - Recreation Schedules (Weekend), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 14)
  - Recreation Schedules (Other), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 15)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 16)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 17)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 18)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 19)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 20)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 21)
  - Sveen, Ann, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 22)
  - Telephone System Bid, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 23)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 24)
  - Whitford, Beverly, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 25)
  - Yaroslasi/Pulse, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 26)
  - Laundry Information, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 27)
  - Evaluation Unit, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 28)
  - Remodeling, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 29)
  - EPP, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 30)
  - Medicaid Inspection, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 31)
  - Austby, Julie, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 1)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 2)
  - Board of Visitors, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 3)
  - Cross, Justin, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 4)
  - Department of Institutions, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 5)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 6)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 7)
  - Chisholm, Curtis, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
  - Currie, James, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 9)
  - Gooch, Thomas, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 10)
  - Personnel Office, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 11)
  - Redfield, Rusty, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 12)
  - Degel, Peter (Dr.), 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 13)
  - Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council (DDPAC), 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 14)
  - Dockter, Larry, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 15)
  - Donation Sheets Received, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 16)
  - Fire Drills, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 17)
  - Fire System Inspections, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 18)
  - Foster Grandparent, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 19)
  - Habilitation, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 20)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 21)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 22)
  - Hammer – Staff Memos, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 23)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 24)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 25)
  - Johnson, Nora, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 26)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 27)
  - Linn, Deb, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 28)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 29)
  - Mast, Jane, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 30)
  - Michelson, Keith, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 31)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 32)
  - MPEA Union, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 33)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 1)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual Update, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 2)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 3)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 4)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 5)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 6)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 7)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 8)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 9)
  - Stansbury, Sheryl, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 10)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 11)
  - Sveen, Ann, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 12)
  - Thilmony, Julie, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 13)
  - Whitford, Beverly, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 14)
  - Yaroslaski, Ann-Marie, 1990 (Box-folder 15 / 15)
  - Austby, Julie, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 16)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 17)
  - Certificates Received, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 18)
  - Cross, Justin M., 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 19)
  - Degel, Peter J., 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 20)
  - Department of Institutions, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 21)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 22)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 23)
  - Chisholm, Curtis, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 24)
  - Currie, James, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 25)
  - Gooch, Thomas, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 26)
  - Personnel Office, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 27)
  - Redfield, Rusty, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 28)
  - Disaster Drills, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 29)
  - Dockter, Larry, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 30)
  - Donation Sheets Received, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 31)
  - Fire Drills, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 32)
  - Fire System Inspections, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 33)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 34)
  - Hammer, Staff Memos, 1991 (Box-folder 15 / 35)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 1)
  - Hansen, Kari, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 2)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 3)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 4)
  - Johnson, Nora, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 5)
  - Johnson – Staff, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 6)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 7)
  - Long Term Care Surveys, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 8)
  - Mast, Jane, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 9)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 10)
  - Olmstead, Maria, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 11)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 12)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 13)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 14)
  - Recreation/Development, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 15)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 16)
  - Recreation Services, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 17)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 18)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 19)
  - Stansbury, Sheryl, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 20)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 21)
  - Sveen, Ann, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 22)
  - Thilmony, Julie, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 23)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1991 (Box-folder 16 / 24)
  - Yaroslaski, Ann-Marie, 1991 (Box-folder 17 / 1)
  - Austby, Julie, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 2)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 3)
  - Board of Visitors, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 4)
  - Burrows, Cashe L., 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 5)
  - Cross, Justin, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 6)
  - Department of Correction and Human Services, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 7)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 8)
  - Chisholm, Curtis, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
  - Dolan, Tom, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 10)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 11)
  - Personnel Office, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 12)
  - Degel, Peter J., 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 13)
  - Dockter, Deborah, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 14)
  - Dufner, Karen, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 15)
  - Fire Drills, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 16)
  - Fire System Inspections, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 17)
  - Gaub, Jane, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 18)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 19)
  - Hammer – Miscellaneous Incoming, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 20)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 21)
  - Hammer – Rule Changes, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 22)
  - Hansen, Kari, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 23)
  - House Bills, 1992 (Box-folder 17 / 24)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 1)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 2)
  - Johnson, Nora, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 3-4)
  - Johnson Staff Memos, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 5)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 6)
  - Mast, Jane, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 7)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 8)
  - Olmstead, Maria, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 9)
  - Over-time/Part-time, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 10)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 11)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 12)
  - Quality Assurance Monitoring, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 13)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 14)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 15)
  - Resident Recommitment Information sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 16)
  - Residential Services, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 17)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 18)
  - Stansbury, Sheryl, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 19)
  - Surveys/Questionnaire, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 20)
  - Sveen, Ann, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 21)
  - Taylor, Loretta, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 22)
  - Thilmony, Julie, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 23)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1992 (Box-folder 18 / 24)
  - Austby, Julie, 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 25)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 26)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 27)
  - Cross, Justin M., 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 28)
  - Degel, Peter J., 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 29)
  - Department of Corrections and Human Services – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 18 / 30)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 1)
  - Chisholm, Curtis, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 2)
  - Dolan, Tom, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 3)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 4)
  - Personnel Division, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 5)
  - Disaster Drill, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 6)
  - Dufner, Karen, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 7)
  - Fire Drills, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 8)
  - Fire System Inspections, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 9)
  - Gaub, Jane, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 10)
  - Hammer Incoming Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 11)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 12)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 13)
  - Hansen, Kari, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 14)
  - Inspections/Audits, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 15)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 16)
  - Johnson, Nora, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 17-18)
  - Johnson Staff Memos, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 19)
  - Job Information from other Agencies, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 20)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 21)
  - Mast, Jane, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 22)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 23)
  - Olmstead, Maria, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 24)
  - Over-time/Part-time Schedules, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 25)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 26)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 27)
  - Quality Assurance Monitoring, 1993 (Box-folder 19 / 28)
  - Recreational/Developmental, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 1)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 2)
  - Request and Justification for Out of State Travel, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 3)
  - Resident Recommitment Information Sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 4)
  - Residential Services, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 5)
  - Reduction in Force (RIF), 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 6)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 7)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 8)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 9)
  - Taylor, Loretta, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 10)
  - Telephone Call Forms, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 11)
  - Thilmony, Julie, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 12)
  - Walla, Susan, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 13)
  - Walter, Douglas A., 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 14)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1993 (Box-folder 20 / 15)
  - Austby, Julie, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 1)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 2)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 3)
  - Berg, Sara, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 4)
  - Department of Corrections and Human Services – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 5)
  - Day, Rick, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 6)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 7)
  - Dolan, Tom, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 8)
  - Dufner, Karen, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 9)
  - Haggerty, Suzanne, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 10-11)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 12)
  - Hammer Incoming Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 13)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 14)
  - Harms, Jane, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 15)
  - Henke, Russ, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 16)
  - Kruger, Jane, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 17)
  - Mast, Jane, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 18)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 19)
  - Over-time/Part-time Schedules, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 20)
  - Olmstead, Maria, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 21)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 22)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 23)
  - Rathbun, Mary, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 24)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 25)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 26)
  - Resident Recommitment Information Sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 27)
  - Residential Services, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 28)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 29)
  - Schatzman, Bard, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 30)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 31)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 32)
  - Thilmony, Julie, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 33)
  - Walla, Susan, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 34)
  - Walter, Douglas A., 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 35)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1994 (Box-folder 21 / 36)
  - Anderson, Bob, 1995 (Box-folder 21 / 37)
  - Austby, Julie, 1995 (Box-folder 21 / 28)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 1)
  - Berg, Sara, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 2)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 3)
  - Contract Professionals, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 4)
  - Day, Rick, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 5)
  - Dolan, Tom, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 6)
  - Haggerty, Suzy, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 7-8)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 9)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 10)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 11)
  - Harms, Jane, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 12)
  - Holsinger, Peggy, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 13)
  - Henke, Russ, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 14)
  - Junso, Pamela, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 15)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 16)
  - Lane, Nancy, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 17)
  - Mast, Jane C., 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 18)